Young Master Hikaru,
the source of the Gero family's inherent
modified bloodline, the poison blood.
It grows exponentially more powerful
the closer that you come to death.
In other words, its potency is
proportionate to your natural lifespan.
The earliest you can obtain the next level
of potency will be no
sooner than 20 years.
Achieving it will be your sole
focus for the next two decades.
The ripening of a perfect and incurable
poison but until that exalted day arrives?
You are forbidden from taking
risks that might lead to an
overdose you may be Fit to
leave the poison clan one day.
Three doses?
But, Gato...
You don't know when to quit, do you?
I mean, three doses?
After an overdose like that,
you've got to hurt like hell!
But an overdose will still kill you.
You must grow accustomed
to toxins gradually,
repeatedly surviving
near fatal attacks in his
attempt to find a bride
has reaped its rewards,
the poison blood of Hikaru Gero.
These encounters have aged his blood
with decades of compressed experience,
allowing it to prematurely
mutate to the next level.
I want marriage.
He has achieved the next stage.
His powers have fastened.
Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan
and his greatest challenge yet,
to get married.
Let's go!
Kill again, can't kill again?
He did it.
Hikaru Gedo, these attacks of yours?
Are you trying to bore me to death?
Don't you know what I've
accomplished the mountain of corpses
I've built A monument of pride
for the five great families
Your poison's useless on me!
After all I've got your blood
flowing through my veins?
Gator's performance, his
lethal dose has multiplied.
He's gotten faster since we fought.
But still, it's not enough.
There's no denying you're the most
gifted genius of our generation.
It took years of rigorous
preparation to gain this power.
And here you jump to the
front of the line to rival it.
And it really pisses me off.
Talk about a waste.
You want to know why, ghetto?
I'll tell you why.
A talent like yours should
be used for killing.
And all you want is to protect your
buddies like you're some kind of hero.
An assassin who saves lives?
Your whole life is a dumb joke.
You'll need more than that to take me out.
You look so cool and
collected but I bet you
can barely stand from
here on out your skill
and Talent aren't gonna help you this is a
match between assassins
it's kill or be killed.
So you better act like one
unless you want to die!
The time has finally come.
To play my ultimate ace in the hole!
Beast blood unleashed.
The hundred beast stampede.
The 93 animals of Jiaco reemerge as one.
A supreme and feral primal cascade.
You're right about me, you know.
It passed through him my
bloodlust ran out ages ago.
There's only one thing I want now to
find happiness like a normal person.
He's dodging them so fast I can't even see
it how does he have the strength for that?
I realized something in my
search for a bride with Kinosaki.
I can't grab hold of the
happiness I want, not on my own.
If I want it, I've got to
lend a helping hand to others.
That's the only way I'll find happiness.
Time to put an end to this, Beastmaster.
Corporal Kodoku.
It is the intrinsic power that
harnesses the potential of one's blood.
The numerous poisons in your body devour
each other over time, evolve into an apex.
This incremental growth is the engine that
unleashes the abilities
of the modified bloodline.
Carved by the events of history into
the hearts of the five great families.
The effects of your toxin.
They all depend on the nature of the
Corporal Kodoku you manage to cultivate.
But once you've mastered
it, it will be incurable.
A poison that kills anything
it touches without pain.
The final stage.
Poison blood unleashed.
A single radiant burst.
That was a lot of build-up for nothing!
Do I have to keep reminding
you I'm immune to your...
What the hell kind of poison is this?
I can't purge it fast enough!
Oh, is that how it is?
You made the big leap.
You got yourself the super-ultra-premium
poison blood, didn't you?
What's going on with his arms?
I feel like I should thank him.
I've finally got a reason to
soar to the ultimate height.
Don't need this!
Or this one!
Or that one!
I only need to keep the parts
that are meant for killing.
A beast built for assassination!
Come at me with everything you've got!
I'll lap up every last drop of your blood!
I'll stuff my gut full of your visceral!
Indulging that hunger!
That's the nature of an assassin!
I'm a poison master.
Do you really think I'd
ever come at you head on?
Not how we do it.
I can't see shit.
What the hell did you do to me, Gero?
Hey, come on!
I can't even hear my voice.
Where am I?
It will be incurable, a poison that
kills all that it touches without fail.
The final stage, that is the
apotheosis of the Poison Master.
Is this really it?
I just die?
This is how I go?
So this shit ton of effort
was for nothing at all?
Not to mention all the prey I've consumed.
This is it.
My fangs just weren't long
enough to reach them in the end.
And if this is truly how I'm going out,
then I'm wringing out the last dregs of
what little life force I've got left.
And I'm dragging every single
one of you to hell with me!
Hey, Gato.
These worthless nobodies are more
valuable than your own life rights.
We fought one-on-one.
Now this is where you lose!
One-on-one?
Nah, wrong again.
Ah, did I keep you waiting? Zoey!
The Hamster Master!
What the hell is going on?
Why can't I move?
Why?
Why is she standing?
She's the weakest among us.
Listen, everyone!
I understand how you feel.
How scared you are.
We're up against a king who's absorbed
and controls countless beasts.
And those animals have all
given in to the rage within him.
But still, we can't forget who we are.
We're masters.
And those aren't just any
beasts he's merged with.
Befriending the wild and the feral.
It's our greatest skill.
so remember those animals
are not our enemies they're
each precious and irreplaceable
there or our other half.
How dare you, you worthless cattle!
They called out to the beasts
within me, and they won them back!
You see, Beastmaster, this fight
was never just between you and me.
This was everyone fighting to
break free from your shackles.
This is bullshit, you grubby little worms!
I knew you'd come through.
Thanks, Hamstermaster.
Ha!
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
So happy.
Of the beast blood a
passage marked by the 13th
birthday when children of
the beast clan's main Family
are given their lifelong
partners by the head of
the clan Toshiro is honest
intelligent I would even
say he's fit to lead the
clan when that day comes
a tiger no a wolf would
best suit him It is time our
wise leader has made a
decision he will now bestow
Toshiro Daigo with the
beast he deems most fitting.
Why?
Why would he?
I humbly accept your most gracious gift.
His eyes alone said it all.
You'll never be fit to lead this clan.
Nothing suits you better than
a scrawny rat with wings!
But I know the truth you were
terrified of my skill you knew
that I could push you out and
take over the clan didn't you?
Well fine then if that's what
you think of me why the hell not?
I'll gladly kill your
old ass and take over!
It was your choice.
I'm still alive, but why?
Gato's the heir to the poison clan,
and he hit me with what has to be
the deadliest toxin on the planet.
Why would he ever let me live? Why?
The effect your toxin has on others,
it all depends on the nature of the Corporal
Kodoku you work to cultivate over time.
The toxin in you reflects my will.
I never set out to see you
dead, or even beat you.
My intent was to save
Arashiyama and the others.
The blood of the five great families.
It's a curse.
We're born to either kill or be killed.
The only life we have is dog-eat-dog.
Quit lying to yourself and admit it.
Our blood is not a curse.
My life, it's all the proof I
need to show you you're wrong.
I'm into DIY candy kits.
I like things that take
some work and time.
Does that sound like a curse?
Sounds like you're an idiot
Mr.
Beastmaster, be honest with me.
Do you have any other dangerous plans?
If you don't come clean, I'll -
Byakko!
The hell are you doing?
Master Toshino
We could still start over.
I'm with you.
Till the end.
They're not getting away?
And just who are you?
Apologies for the trouble
my brother has caused.
Since you asked, I'm the newly
appointed head of our Beast Clan,
Tonico Dogo.
But Beast Master is just fine.
Ah, the
out-to-na-ni-yo-i-wa-ta-si-bick-ri-do-ki-ri-fum-da-ri-ke-ta-ri-bu-ga-mu-chu
Ah,
the
out-to-na-ni-yo-i-ya-na-ta-ha-ta-ri-ba-kari-un-zari-gakari-bye-bye
I'll be creepy, oh, fake that voice
Ah,
I'm not sure how to do my life I
am not sure how to do my problems
I'm thinking about the realities
I'm so happy with my life I want to
experience damage I'm gonna be full
of love I'm really quite a good hat
I'll be fine with my
normal reputation I'm going
to give you a great hat
I'm really quite a good hat
I'm so happy to have a great
game I'm gonna be great
How do I think this is so?
Leave it to me.
I promise not I've never been better.
I like you.
Next time. Thanks, man.